<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PacketDirect on PacketFabric</title>
    <link>/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PacketDirect on PacketFabric</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 15:14:39 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Select the Package</title>
      <link>/docs/create-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/create-package/</guid>
      <description>To order a PacketDirect point-to-point service, first log in to the PacketFabric portal and click on the Network tab:
Then select Packages:
Next, to add a new package, click on the plus button at the top right:
and click SELECT PacketDirect.
Clicking the SELECT button takes us to the Select Source Port Market screen, described in the next section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Select Source Port Market</title>
      <link>/docs/selectsourceport/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 16:32:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/selectsourceport/</guid>
      <description>Start by choosing a source port from any of our locations. Here, we’ll choose Chicago. There are multiple Chicago options; we’ll choose Coresite CH1 in Chicago:
Once we select Chicago and Coresite CH1, we see the below screen. The green checkmark overlay indicates that we have successfully chosen our Source Port Market and Site.
We can now select available source port details. We’ll choose the 10Gbps/LR radio button:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Select Destination Port Market</title>
      <link>/docs/selectdestinationport/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 22:08:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/selectdestinationport/</guid>
      <description>Next: ‘Select Destination Port Market.’ We’ll choose our destination port; let&amp;rsquo;s select Los Angeles:
Once we’ve chosen a city we’re again presented with a list of available sites. We’ll select Equinix LA1:
Once we do that, we again see the green checkmark. Notice that as we advance through each step in the process, we get continuous and cumulative feedback on our selections. We can at any time revise any of these selections by clicking, thus far, CHANGE SOURCE LOCATION, CHANGE SOURCE DETAILS, CHANGE DESTINATION LOCATION.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Activate The Service</title>
      <link>/docs/activatetheservice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 23:00:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/activatetheservice/</guid>
      <description>Once our PacketDirect service is finished provisioning, we generate the Letters of Authorization (LOAs). We do that by clicking on the three dots on the far right-hand side and choosing ‘generate LOA:’
We’ll now choose to:
 Generate the LOA for both sides at the same time, without selecting the option to email as an attachment Change who the LOA is made out to. (If, for instance if we’re known as a different name at a facility we can go ahead and put that name in, as we’ve done below &amp;ndash; “Brand X&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>